https://flagladyusa.com/privacy-policy

My Wishlist
Quisque iaculis rhoncus orci eu suscipit lorem sodales at. Fusce ac metus ut metus adipiscing dapibus ut ac leo.
Login
Forgot Your Password?
New Customer ?
Create An Acount
Shopping Cart ( 0 item )
Spend $150, Get FREE SHIPPING
OR $9 Flat Rate Shipping
icon
Shopping Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
USA Lapel Pins
Did You Know?
The American Flag is the backbone of our company. Our founder, Mary Leavitt The Flag Lady - started selling the American Flag out of the trunk of her car during the Iranian crisis.
Now 34 years later, our family owned & operated business has grown into one of the largest flag dealers in the country. We have been blessed and we thank you for all of your support!
Flags
International Flags
Africa
Asia
Europe
North America
Oceania
South America
Christian Flags
Catholic Flags (Papal)
Episcopal Flags
Israeli Flags
Presbyterian Flags
Other Flags
Nautical Flags
Racing Flags
Warning Flags
Golf Flags
Can't Find What You Want?
If we don't have it, we'll find it. If we can't find it, we'll make it!
If you're having trouble finding the flag that you're looking for please call us 1-800-797-3524
Flagpoles
Commercial Flagpoles
Special Budget Series
Atlas Series
Architectural Series
Fiberglass Commercial Flagpoles
Outrigger Flagpoles
External Halyard Flagpoles
More Accessories
Need Installation?
We have a full installation service that can handle all of your flagpole installation needs.
Our dedicated service staff can handle large scale commercial installations as well as residential installations. Ask us about our flag rotation service as well.
Custom Flags
Custom Flags
Digitally Dyed Flags
Sewn Flags
Feather Flags
Sunblade Flags
Teardrop Flags
Custom Banners
Stand Out Banners
Need Something Else?
If you can dream it, we can probably make it. If you're not seeing the product that you'd like please give us a call 1-800-797-3524
Military & Civil
Service Branch Flags
Air Force
Army
Coast Guard
Marine Corps
Navy
POW/MIA
Ohio University
Miami (OH)
Independents
University of Notre Dame
NFL
AFC - North
Baltimore Ravens
Cincinnati Bengals
Cleveland Browns
Pittsburgh Steelers
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: ; To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) ; To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) ; To process transactions Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. ; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature ; To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. Do we use cookies? We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.
These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy. Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http://www.flagladyusa.com 4567 N. High Street Columbus, Ohio 43214 USA Support@flagladyusa.com
Additional Helpful Links
Helpful Links
Contact Us
FAQs
Shipping Information
Return Policy
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
